// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "It determines how near you are to the measurement's real value. In other words, it's how closely you hit your target",
    answer: "Accuracy",
    options: [
      "Precision",
      "Accuracy",
      "Gravitational Force",
      "London Dispersion Force"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "It indicates how near the measured values are to each other.",
    answer: "Precision",
    options: [
      "Accuracy",
      "Precision",
      "SuperStar",
      "Kinetic Energy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "You hit your target value exactly",
    answer: "High accuracy",
    options: [
      "Low accuracy",
      "High Volume",
      "Precise",
      "High accuracy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "It can be measured throughout the time.",
    answer: "Precision",
    options: [
      "Precision",
      "Saturated Solution",
      "Accuracy",
      "High accuracy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " The arrows are scattered all over place and does not hit the target.",
    answer: "Low precision",
    options: [
      "Low precision",
      "High Precesion",
      "High Accuracy",
      "Dilute Solution"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 6,
    question: "It is required to evaluate the degree of similarity between each set of measurements.",
    answer: "Repeatability",
    options: [
      "Persistent",
      "Repeatability",
      "Decisive",
      "Infatuation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "You considerably miss the target.",
    answer: "Low accuracy",
    options: [
      "Negative Energy",
      "High Precision",
      "High accuracy",
      "Low accuracy"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 8,
    question: "A basketball players consistently shoot the ball.",
    answer: "High precision and high accuracy",
    options: [
      "Low accuracy",
      "High precision and high accuracy",
      "poor precision",
      "High accuracy Low precision"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "All the darts are scattered all over the dart board, 1 dart hits the bull-eye, and other darts are far to one another.",
    answer: "poor precision and poor accuracy",
    options: [
      "poor precision and poor accuracy",
      "High precision and high accuracy",
      "High precision",
      "High accuracy"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 10,
    question: "The arrows are close to each other but does not hit the target.",
    answer: "High precision",
    options: [
      "Low precision",
      "High precision",
      "Poor accuracy",
      "High accuracy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "You hit the bulls-eye consistently",
    answer: "High precision and high accuracy",
    options: [
      "Low accuracy",
      "High precision and high accuracy",
      "poor precision",
      "High accuracy and Low precision"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 12,
    question: "Darts landed scattered, but it is all close to the target.",
    answer: "High accuracy and Low precision",
    options: [
      "Low accuracy",
      "High precision and high accuracy",
      "poor precision",
      "High accuracy and Low precision"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "It is the consistency of outcomes when measurements are repeated.",
    answer: "Precision",
    options: [
      "Accuracy",
      "Precision",
      "Sequence",
      "BUll's eye"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 14,
    question: "When a set of measurements are close but not equal to the true value.",
    answer: "Precision",
    options: [
      "Accuracy",
      "Precision",
      "Sequence",
      "BUll's eye"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "When a series of measurements are considered close to the true value.",
    answer: "Accuracy",
    options: [
      "Accuracy",
      "Precision",
      "Sequence",
      "BUll's eye"
    ]
  },
]